Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 1986
    - Salute to Immigrant Cultures / Statue of Liberty Centennial, July 1986
      - Moving Images, 1986-07-05
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0705_1.30-1.35; Note on media: 1.30: West Indian Dancers; ADJA 1.31: Son de la Loma 1.32: Musica Popolare; Samul Nori 1.33: Samul Nori; Sister Sadie and the Famous Biblettes 1.34: Sister Sadie and the Famous Biblettes; Engetsu Daiko; 1.35: Engetsu Daiko; Los Pregoneros del Puerto
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0705_1.36-1.42; Note on media: 1.36: Los Pregoneros del Puerto; Green Fields of America 1.37: Green Fields of America 1.38: West Indian steel band 1.39: West Indian steel band; ADJA 1.40: ADJA (no audio) 1.41: Son de la Loma (no audio) 1.42: Son de la Loma (audio on channel 1 only)
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0705_1.43, 86-0706_1.1-1.6; Note on media: 1.1-1.6: Conjunto Libre
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0705_dvcam1.18-1.24
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0705_dvcam1.3-1.8
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0705_dvcam1.9-11
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0705_dvcam30-35
      - Moving Images, 1986-07-06
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-1; Note on media: Conjunto Libre
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-2; Note on media: Conjunto Libre
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-3; Note on media: Conjunto Libre
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-4; Note on media: Conjunto Libre - audio CH 1 only
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-5; Note on media: Conjunto Libre - audio CH 1 only
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-6; Note on media: Conjunto Libre
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-7; Note on media: Conjunto Libre - audio CH 1 only
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-8; Note on media: Popovich Brothers
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-9; Note on media: Popovich Brothers; Voices of The Earth
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-10; Note on media: Voices of The Earth; Demotika
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-11; Note on media: Demotika; El Sexteto
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-12; Note on media: El Sexto
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-13; Note on media: Music of China
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-14; Note on media: Music of China; Anjani Ambegaokar
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-15; Note on media: Popovich Brothers; Voices of The Earth
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-16; Note on media: Voices of The Earth
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-17; Note on media: Demotika; El Sexteto
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-18; Note on media: El Sexto
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-19; Note on media: Music of China; Anjani Ambegaokar
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-20; Note on media: Popovich Brothers
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-21; Note on media: Popovich Brothers; Voices of The Earth
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-22; Note on media: Voices of The Earth; Demotika; El Sexteto
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-23; Note on media: El Sexteto; Music of China; Anjani Ambegaokar
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-24; Note on media: Anjani Ambegaokar
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1-30; Note on media: Post-concert interviews with audience
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-01; Note on media: Tapes A1-A3, stage 1
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-02; Note on media: Tapes B1-B2, C1
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-03; Note on media: Tape C2, stages 1 and 2 [possibly also tapes A1 and A2]
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-04; Note on media: Stage 2, tapes A3-A5-A6; time missing between A3-A5
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-05; Note on media: Stages 2 and 3, tapes B1, B2, miscellaneous
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-06; Note on media: Stage 2, tapes B5, C1, C2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-07; Note on media: Stage 2, tape C3; not listed on the inventory
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-08; Note on media: Tapes A1-A2, C3; not on the inventory
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_02-09; Note on media: Tapes B4, C1, interviews; not on inventory
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_03-1; Note on media: 3.1/ stage 1 and 2, C1, A1-3, A5-6
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_03-2; Note on media: 3.2/ stage 2 and 3, B1-2, misc., B5, C1-2
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_03-3; Note on media: 3.3/ stage 2 C3 only
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1.13-1.18; Note on media: 1.13: Music of China 1.14: Music of China; Anjani Ambegaokar 1.15: Popovich Brothers; Voices of the Earth 1.16: Voices of the Earth 1.17: Demotika; El Sexteto 1.18: El Sexteto
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1.19-1.23; Note on media: 1.19: China; Anjani Ambegaokar 1.20: Popovich Brothers: 1.21: Popovich Brothers; Voices of the Earth 1.22: Voices of the Earth; Demotika; El Sexteto 1.23: El Sexteto; China
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 64 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1.24-1.30; Note on media: 1.24: Anjani Ambegaokar 1.30: interviews with audience
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 86-0706_1.7-1.12; Note on media: 1.7: Libre 1.8: Popovich Brothers; Voices of the Earth; Demotika 1.9: Popovich Brothers; Voices of the Earth 1.11: Demotika; El Sexteto 1.12: El Sexteto
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0706_dvcam1.13-18
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0706_dvcam1.19-1.23
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0706_1.24and1.30
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., SOL 86-0706_dvcam1.7-12
    - Queens Ethnic Music and Dance Festival, September 1986
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1986-09-20
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Eleventh Annual Queens Ethnic Music and Dance Festival (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Moving Images, 1986-09-20
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_1; Note on media: test tape?
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_2; Note on media: test tape?
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_3; Note on media: DeFranco Family
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_4; Note on media: DeFranco Family
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_5; Note on media: Bukharan Jewish Ensemble
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_6; Note on media: Bukharan Jewish Ensemble
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_7; Note on media: Interviews; crowd scenes
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_8; Note on media: Pepe Castillo y Bomplena
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_9; Note on media: Pepe Castillo y Bomplena
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_10; Note on media: Pepe Castillo y Bomplena
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_11; Note on media: Los Amigos del Ritmo
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_12; Note on media: Pepe Castillo
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_13; Note on media: Pepe Castillo; John Berberian Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_14; Note on media: John Berberian Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_15; Note on media: John Berberian / Ilias Kementzides
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_16; Note on media: Ilias Kementzides
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_17; Note on media: Ilias Kementzides; Halkias
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_18; Note on media: Halkias
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_19; Note on media: Halkias
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_20; Note on media: [content undetermined]
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_21; Note on media: test tape
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_22; Note on media: Bukharan Jewish Ensemble
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_23; Note on media: Introduction to Pepe Castillo
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_24; Note on media: Pepe Castilla y Bomplena
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_25; Note on media: John Roussos; Greek dancing
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_26; Note on media: John Roussos; Greek dancing; Los Amigo del Ritmo
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_27; Note on media: Los Amigo del Ritmo
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_28; Note on media: Los Amigos del Ritnmo; Pushka Pukna Bulgarian Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_29; Note on media: Pepe Castillo y Bomplena
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_30; Note on media: Pepe Castillo y Bomplena
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_31; Note on media: [content undetermined]
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_32; Note on media: John Berberian Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_33; Note on media: end of John Berberian Orchestra; Ilias Kementzides and Panayiotis Vassiliades
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_34; Note on media: Ilias Kementzides and Panayiotis Vassiliades
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_35; Note on media: Pericles Halkias Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_36; Note on media: Pericles Halkias Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_2-10, 11 (camera A)
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_12A-17A
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_18A-19A
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_21-28
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_28-35
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 86-0920_36
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 86-0920_12A-17A
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 86-0920_dvcam-18A-20A
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 86-0920_21-28
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 86-0920_dvcam28-35
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 86-0920_dvcam36-40
    - Other events, 1986
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1986-01-04, Note on folder: Fathers and Daughters (Box-folder 4/31)
        - 1 folder, 1986-02, Note on folder: Eastern European Film Series (Box-folder 4/33)
        - 1 folder, 1986-02-22, Note on folder: Fiddler's Choice - Cherish the Ladies (Box-folder 4/32)
        - 1 folder, 1986-05-27, Note on folder: Lady Liberty Gala program (Box-folder 4/34)
        - 1 folder, 1986-12-12; 1986-12-14, Note on folder: Nineteenth Annual Winter Folk Festival (Box-folder 5/3)
        - 1 folder, 1986-1987, Note on folder: Folk Arts Program - NY State Council on the Arts (Box-folder 5/4)
        - 1 folder, 1986-1987, Note on folder: Misc. Fliers for Folk Dance Classes (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Events, 1987
    - Irish Family Music, February 1987
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1987-02-28
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Moving Images, 1987-02-28
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_01; Note on media: Eagan Family. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_02; Note on media: Eagan Family. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_03; Note on media: Donny and Eileen Golden. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_04; Note on media: Brendan and Martin Mulvihill. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_05; Note on media: Brendan and Martin Mulvihill. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_06; Note on media: Brigid / Mick Maloney. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_07; Note on media: Eagan Family. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_08; Note on media: Ceilidh / Dance. Venue: Merkin Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic), AFC 2014/044: EMCS 87-0228_09
    - SOL - Ilias Kementzides, July 1987
      - Moving Images, 1987-07-03
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_01
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_02
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_03
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_04
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_05
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_06
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_07
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_08
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_09
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_02-1
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_02-2
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0703_02-3
    - SOL, September 1987
      - Moving Images, 1987-09-02 to 1987-09-03
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-1; Note on media: Albert Rashid
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-2; Note on media: Albert Rashid
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-3; Note on media: Albert Rashid
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-4; Note on media: Albert Rashid
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-5; Note on media: Ray Rashid. Venue. Tripoli Restaurant
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-6; Note on media: Simon Shaheen interview. Venue. Tripoli Restaurant
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-7; Note on media: Simon Shaheen performance. Venue. Tripoli Restaurant
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_01-8; Note on media: Simon Shaheen performance
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_02-1; Note on media: Albert Rashid
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_02-2; Note on media: Albert Rashid
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_03-1; Note on media: 3.1/ Albert Rashina 01,02,03,04 Ray 05 Simon 06
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-1; Note on media: Jack Coen
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-2; Note on media: Jack Coen
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-3; Note on media: Jack Coen and Mick Maloney
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-4; Note on media: Jack Coen and Mick Maloney
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-5; Note on media: Jack Coen and Mick Maloney
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-6; Note on media: Jack Coen and Mick Maloney
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_01-7; Note on media: Jack Coen and Mick Maloney
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_02-1; Note on media: Jack Coen
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_02-2; Note on media: Jack Coen
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0902_03-2, 87-0903_03-1; Note on media: 3.1/3.2/ Simon Kripali Pert 07 + 08/ Jack Coen 01,02,03,04 (mick)
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-0903_03-2; Note on media: 3.2/ Mick and Jack 05 06 07 + NJHS/ Sept 86 OF Bukhams
    - SOL, October 1987
      - Moving Images, 1987-10-07
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_1-1; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_1-2; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_1-3; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_1-4; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_1-5; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_02-1; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_02-2; Note on media: Bernice Johnson Reagon
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1007_03-1; Note on media: 3.1/ Bernice Reagon
      - Moving Images, 1987-10-22
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-1; Note on media: Andy Gonzalez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-2; Note on media: Andy Gonzalez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-3; Note on media: Andy Gonzalez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-4; Note on media: Andy Gonzalez and Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-5; Note on media: Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-6; Note on media: Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-7; Note on media: Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-8; Note on media: Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-9; Note on media: Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-10; Note on media: Ramon Vasquez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_1-11; Note on media: El Caney del Barrio. Notes: Plena y Bomba
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_02-1; Note on media: Andy Gonzalez
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_02-2; Note on media: Andy Gonzalez; Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_02-3; Note on media: Israel Berrios
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_02-4; Note on media: Ramon Vasquez; Plena y Bomba
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_03-1; Note on media: 3.1/ Andy Gonzalez/ Israel Berrios :05 :06 :07
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1022_03-2; Note on media: 3.2/ Israel Berrios 8 9+10/ Ramon Vasquez :11 Pleno y Bomba
      - Moving Images, 1987-10-29
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_1-1; Note on media: Rene Lopez
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_1-2; Note on media: Rene Lopez
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_1-3; Note on media: Rene Lopez
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_4; Note on media: Rene Lopez
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_5; Note on media: Rene Lopez
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_6; Note on media: Jose, Sammy, David
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_7; Note on media: Jose, Sammy, David
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_8; Note on media: Jose, Sammy, David
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_9
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_10; Note on media: Pablo, Paco, Eugenia
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_02-1; Note on media: Rene Lopez
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_02-2; Note on media: Rene Lopez; Jose, Sammy, David
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_02-3; Note on media: Jose, Sammy, David; Pablo, Paco, Eugenia
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_02-4, 87-1103-02-1; Note on media: Pablo, Paco, Eugenia; Juan Gutierrez
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_03-1; Note on media: 3.1/ Rene Lopez/ Jose, Sammy and David (ihcomp)
        - 1 videocassette (VHS; 120 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1029_03-2; Note on media: 3.2/ Jose Rivera, Sammy Tanco, Davia Rosario, Pabls, Paco, Euqeria :06(end only), :07 :08 :09/ Juan Gutierrez 01 + 02
    - SOL, November 1987
      - Moving Images, 1987-11-03
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-1; Note on media: Juan Gutierrez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-2; Note on media: Juan Gutierrez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-3; Note on media: Juan Gutierrez
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-4; Note on media: Juan Gutierrez
        - 1 videocassette (Betamax; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-5; Note on media: Juan Gutierrez and Tito Cepeda
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-6; Note on media: Tito Cepeda, church exterior, Sister Sadie Interview
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-7; Note on media: Sadie and the Famous Biblettes
        - 1 videocassette (Betacam; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: SOL 87-1103_1-8; Note on media: Sadie and the Famous Biblettes